Guide to the New York State Board of Mediation Cases 1952-1964
New York State Board of Mediation Cases
- ME304 - ME561 (1957). (Box 113)
  - ME-370 Central Luncheonette, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 35)
  - ME-371 A. Simkins Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 36)
  - ME-372 Goodwear Luggage Store, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 37)
  - ME-373 Carter, Milchman & Frank, Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 38)
  - ME-374 North Shore Motor Sales, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 39)
  - ME-375 Merit Pain Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 40)
  - ME-377 Sapleon & Schneider Motor Sales Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 41)
  - ME-379 Neptune Storage, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 42)
  - ME-180 Inwood "Y" (Washington Heights), 1957 (Box 113, Folder 43)
  - ME-382 A. Russo & Sons, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 44)
  - ME-384 Sunset Appliance, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 45)
  - ME-386 157 Vemilyea Ave., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 46)
  - ME-388 Euclid Candy Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 47)
  - ME-390 Defender Embroidery Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 48)
  - ME-391 Flack Footwear Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 49)
  - ME-392 National Gypsum Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 50)
  - ME-394 Olympia Provision & Baking, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 51)
  - ME-395 Philip H. Harris Button Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 52)
  - ME-397 International Cut Rate Stores, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 53)
  - ME-398 James F. Waters, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 54)
  - ME-399 Development Corp. For Israel, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 55)
  - ME-400 Woodall Industries, Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 56)
  - ME-403 Embassy Grocery Corp., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 57)
  - ME-405 122 East 25th Street, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 58)
  - ME-406 Arbuck Inc. ARB 4232, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 59)
  - ME-407 Crownola Looseleaf Products, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 60)
  - ME-409 Larsen Baking Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 61)
  - ME-411 N.Y. Assn. of Wholesalers of Ladies & Children's Hats, Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 62)
  - ME-412 Alvin Schwartz Chevrolet, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 63)
  - ME-414 West Luncheonette, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 64)
  - ME-416 Benrus Watch Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 65)
  - ME-417 L.I. State Parkway Commission, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 66)
  - ME-419 Nassau Bus Line Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 67)
  - ME-420 Hartman Home Crest, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 68)
  - ME-421 Columbia Records, Div. of CBS, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 69)
  - ME-424 Greene Construction Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 70)
  - ME-426 Styl-Rite Optics Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 71)
  - ME-429 Bush Terminal Bldgs., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 72)
  - ME-430 Keystone Garter, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 73)
  - ME-431 Pennsylvania Window Cleaning, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 74)
  - ME-432 48 Wall Street, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 75)
  - ME-433 Ames Manufacturing Corp., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 76)
  - ME-435 J.W. Wilson Glass Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 77)
  - ME-436 Arcade Restaurant, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 78)
  - ME-438 Perfo-Mat & Rubber Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 79)
  - ME-439 Wallstein Industrial Corp., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 80)
  - ME-441 Consolidated Decorating Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 81)
  - ME-442 Carey Airlines, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 82)
  - ME-443 New York Skyport Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 83)
  - ME-444 E. G. Young Lumber Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 84)
  - ME-448 145 Hicks Street, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 85)
  - ME-449 Great Neck Oaks, #2, #3, #4, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 86)
  - ME-450 Burken Lamination Corp., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 87)
  - ME-453 Dairy Transport Assn., 1955-1957 (Box 113, Folder 88)
  - ME-457 Continental Engraving Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 89)
  - ME-458 Metropolitan Container Council Association, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 90)
  - ME-459 1259 Leland Avenue, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 91)
  - ME-460 Northside Plating Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 92)
  - ME-462 Triangle Steel Door, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 93)
  - ME-463 Jaeger Watch Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 94)
  - ME-467 Affiliated Restaurateurs, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 95)
  - ME-469 Pioneer Steel Door, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 96)
  - ME-480 368 Eastern Parkway, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 97)
  - ME-482 Parkway Village Apartments, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 98)
  - ME-484 Spence Engineering Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 99)
  - ME-485 K & SW Cleaners & Dyers, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 100)
  - ME-486 Massapequa Junior High School, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 101)
  - ME-490 National Lead Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 102)
  - ME-492 Lundy's Restaurant, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 103)
  - ME-496 Crown Die Casting, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 104)
  - ME-497 Sainberg & Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 105)
  - ME-502 Cast Fittings Corp., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 106)
  - ME-505 Antico Mfg. Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 107)
  - ME-509 1819 Weeks Avenue, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 108)
  - ME-510 Long Island Water Corp., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 109)
  - ME-511 Dispensers, Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 110)
  - ME-512 Marketmen's Association, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 111)
  - ME-513 1583 Macombs Rd., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 112)
  - ME-517 143-54 Roosevelt Avenue, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 113)
  - ME-518 J. Hasday & Sons Optical Mfg. Co., 1954 (Box 113, Folder 114)
  - ME-520 A. J. Radin, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 115)
  - ME-522 Meadow Gold Ice Cream, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 116)
  - ME-524 30-36 Magaw Place, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 117)
  - ME-526 Regal Bag Corporation, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 118)
  - ME-529 Westchester Country Club, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 119)
  - ME-530 Joseph A. Kaplan & Sons, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 120)
  - ME-534 Edro Photo Service, Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 121)
  - ME-536 Theatrical Costumers, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 122)
  - ME-537 Master Transit Mix Corp., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 123)
  - ME-539 Rugby Francis Corp., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 124)
  - ME-541 United Contact Lens Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 125)
  - ME-542 Click Chemical Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 126)
  - ME-543 S & S Sheet Metal Works, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 127)
  - ME-544 690 & 700 East 139th Street, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 128)
  - ME-545 Finesse Wristlet, Inc., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 129)
  - ME-548 Salta Bedspread, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 130)
  - ME-549 New York Notion Company and Center Slide Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 131)
  - ME-550 Penn Products Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 132)
  - ME-551 Milk Handlers & Processors, Inc. (Receiving Plants), 1957 (Box 113, Folder 133)
  - ME-552 Milk Handlers & Professors, Inc. (New York & New Jersey), 1957 (Box 113, Folder 134)
  - ME-553 Arwood Casting Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 135)
  - ME-556 Helmar Mfg. Company, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 136)
  - ME-557 630 Broadway, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 137)
  - ME-558 Tally Ho Trading, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 138)
  - ME-559 Pioneer Women, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 139)
  - ME-560 Burkart Brothers Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 140)
  - ME-561 1080 Warburton Ave., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 141)
- ME563 - ME685 (1957). (Box 114)
  - ME-628 3505 Rochambeau Avenue, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - ME-630 Long Island Water Corp., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - ME-632 Oakwood Trucking, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - ME-633 Keystone Hotel, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - ME-634 Kings Electronics Co., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - ME-635 Metro Sacks, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - ME-642 Crusader Mfg. Company, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - ME-643 Pioneer Ice Cream Division (The Borden Co), 1957 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - ME-644 Pollard-Alling Manufacturing Co., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - ME-646 Best Curtain Company, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - ME-647 Infant Formula Laboratory Service, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - ME-648 960 Hoe Avenue, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - ME-649 1445 Nelson Avenue, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - ME-650 Mutual Sewing Machine Dealers, Assn., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - ME-658 Mohegan Stores, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - ME-660 Zellman & Friedman, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - ME-664 1065 Woodycrest Avenue, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - ME-665 Robin-Skall Display Case Co., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - ME-666 Birnbach Radio Corp., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - ME-667 Nassau Smelting & Refining Co., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - ME-669 Refrigeration & Air Conditioning Contractors Assn., 1954 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - ME-672 American Guild of Variety Artists, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - ME-674 Sportservice, Inc., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - ME-676 Mark Cross, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - ME-616 Wave Crest Garden Apartments, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - ME-619 Enteco Industries, Inc., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - ME-620 Hotel Nassau, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - ME-622 Herbert Products Co., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - ME-623 Necco, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 29)
  - ME-625 Rex Electric Mfg. Corp., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 30)
  - ME-626 Kurman Electric Corp., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - ME-627 Art Steel Company, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 32)
  - ME-595 City Wide Processing Service, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 33)
  - ME-597 265 East 176th Street, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 34)
  - ME-599 Winton Food Inc., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 35)
  - ME-600 N.Y. & New England States Boilermakers Employers, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 36)
  - ME-602 A & W Products, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 37)
  - ME-604 A.M.R. Chemical Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 38)
  - ME-605 Ernest Chandler, Inc., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 39)
  - ME-608 Triad Electronics Co., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 40)
  - ME-609 H. M. Storms Company, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 41)
  - ME-610 Amatex Buff Company, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 42)
  - ME-613 Wire Display & Wire Products Industry, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 43)
  - ME-563 United Master Barbers Assn. of Queens, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 44)
  - ME-568 Selva Sons, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 45)
  - ME-570 Warwick Central School, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 46)
  - ME-571 Larchmont Lodge (Abe Levine's), 1957 (Box 114, Folder 47)
  - ME-573 Citroen Cars Corp., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 48)
  - ME-574 Hudson Vitamin Products, Inc., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 49)
  - ME-577 Armour and Company, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 50)
  - ME-578 United Transformer Corp., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 51)
  - ME-580 Acey Oldsmobile, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 52)
  - ME-581 Gurran Oil Company, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 53)
  - ME-587 2095 Cruger Avenue, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 54)
  - ME-589 Consultants Bureau, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 55)
  - ME-590 Rootes Motor, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 56)
  - ME-591 United Brass Works, Inc., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 57)
  - ME-592 Donnelly Blanthorn & Company, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 58)
  - ME-593 Union News, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 59)
  - ME-681 1122 Kelly Street, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 60)
  - ME-685 8609 Caudwell Avenue, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 61)